

Hamza Akrouti

First name: Hamza
Last name: Akrouti
Date of birth: 17/02/1997

Phone number: Email address: Web: (+216) 51465997 akrouti.hamza@yahoo.com akroutihamza.github.io

$(\mathbf{1})$

Profile

Creative Js Developer with strong leadership and relationship building skills.

Executed and contributed to full-stack web development projects, with an emphasis on front end features. Experienced in developing decentralized blockchain applications using Ethereum and hyperledger Blockchain.

Work experience

07/2019 - 08/2019

Junior java Developer
 Tunisia Telecom, Mahdia, Tunisia

02/2020 - 03/2020

Javascript and Blockchain developer

Dar Blockchain , Ariana, Tunisia

02/2020 - 07/2020

Blockchain developer

Lightency Solutions, Paris, France

Education

09/2012 - 07/2017

Tahar Haddad High School

Experimental science, Sidi Bouzid, Tunisia

High school diploma in Sciences

09/2017 - 07/2020

Higher Institute of Computer Science

Computer system and software, Mahdia, Tunisia

Licentiate degree in Computer Science



Projects

FLIGHTINSURRANCE

Distributed app for managing insurance for travelers

Technologies: Ethereum Blockchain, jquery

DCHAIN

Decentralized Voting app

Technologies: Ethereum Blockchain, ReactJS

COVID19 TRACKER

Application for tracking status of COVID-19 pandemic

Technologies: Node is, ReactJS

Publications

07/2020

Consensus Algorithms In Blockchain Systems

Hamza Akrouti

https://medium.com

08/2020

Bitcoin vs Ethereum vs Hyperledger

Hamza Akrouti

https://medium.com

Certificates

11/2016

Fondamentaux du Marketing Digital - Google pour les Pros Google

